(Sheldon:)is for us to sign
and date the document,
(Sheldon:)and we will officially
no longer be roommates.
(Penny:)What's the matter?
(Leonard:)It's harder than I thought.
(Sheldon:)Let me help you.
(Sheldon:)L-E-O-N...
(Leonard:)That helped.
(Raj:)So I have an idea
for a filk song.
(Raj:)Kind of a,
(Raj:)a power ballad,
superhero crossover tale
(Raj:)of epic proportions.
(Howard:)Is it cold in here,
(Howard:)'cause, oh, my.
(Raj:)Okay, so it's a, it's a
David and Goliath story.
(Raj:)It's about man against God.
It's called "Hammer and Whip:
"The Untold Story
of Thor versus Indiana Jones."
(Howard:)Thor versus Indiana Jones?
(Howard:)You just blew my filking mind.
(Raj:)Okay, I don't have it
all worked out yet,
(Raj:)but I was thinking
something like, um...